Guide to the Richard Charles Lee Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Mayoral Files, 1943-1969; Series I; 44 linear feet (106 boxes)
  - 1955
    - Unions (Box 7, Folder 173)
    - U. S. Coast Guard (Box 7, Folder 174)
    - U. S. Conference of Mayors (Box 7, Folder 175)
    - "V" general (Box 7, Folder 176)
    - "W" general (Box 7, Folder 177)
    - Welfare, Department of (Box 7, Folder 178)
    - Wooster Square (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - 1956
    - "A" general (Box 7, Folder 180)
    - Airport (Box 7, Folder 181)
    - Aldermen, Board of (Box 7, Folder 182)
    - Assessors, Board of (Box 7, Folder 183)
    - "B" general (Box 7, Folder 184)
    - "C" general (Box 7, Folder 185)
    - Cabinet (Box 7, Folder 186)
    - Census Tract 16 (Box 7, Folder 187)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 7, Folder 188)
    - Children's Building Commission (Box 7, Folder 189)
    - Citizens Action Commission; education (Box 7, Folder 190)
    - Citizens Action Commission: general (Box 7, Folder 191)
    - Citizens Action Commission: human relations (Box 8, Folder 192)
    - Citizens Action Commission: industrial and harbor development (Box 8, Folder 193)
    - Citizens Action Commission: minutes (Box 8, Folder 194)
    - Citizens Action Commission: Sweet, H. Gordon (Box 8, Folder 195)
    - City Engineer (Box 8, Folder 196)
    - City Hall Project (Box 8, Folder 197)
    - City Plan Department (Box 8, Folder 198)
    - Civil Defense (Box 8, Folder 199)
    - Clean-up campaign (Box 8, Folder 200)
    - Connecticut Company (Box 8, Folder 201)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 8, Folder 202)
    - Controller (Box 8, Folder 203)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 8, Folder 204)
    - Education, Department of (Box 8, Folder 205)
    - Education, Department of; High Schools (Box 8, Folder 206)
    - Education, Department of: High School Sites (Box 8, Folder 207-208)
    - Employees retirement fund (Box 8, Folder 209)
    - Environmental Sanitation, Bureau of (Box 8, Folder 210)
    - Executive Orders (Box 8, Folder 211)
    - "F" general (Box 8, Folder 212)
    - Fiscal Survey Commission (Box 8, Folder 213)
    - Flood Disaster (Box 8, Folder 214)
    - Fluoridation (Box 8, Folder 215)
    - "G" general (Box 8, Folder 216)
    - Grace-New Haven Community Hospital (Box 8, Folder 217)
    - "H" general (Box 8, Folder 218)
    - Harbor (Box 8, Folder 219)
    - Health, Department of (Box 9, Folder 220)
    - Housing Authority (Box 9, Folder 221)
    - Human Relations Council (Box 9, Folder 222)
    - Humane Commission (Box 9, Folder 223)
    - Juvenile delinquency (Box 9, Folder 224)
    - "K" general (Box 9, Folder 225)
    - Knights of Columbus (Box 9, Folder 226)
    - "L" general (Box 9, Folder 227)
    - League of Women Voters (Box 9, Folder 228)
    - Legal Aid Bureau (Box 9, Folder 229)
    - Light of Freedom (Box 9, Folder 230)
    - Logue, Edward J. (Box 9, Folder 231)
    - "M" general (Box 9, Folder 232)
    - Malley, Edward, Co. (Box 9, Folder 233)
    - Mayor's Commission on Unlicensed Attendants (Nurses) (Box 9, Folder 234)
    - N. A. A. C. P. (Box 9, Folder 235)
    - Natural gas legislation (Box 9, Folder 236)
    - Oak Street Connector (Box 9, Folder 237)
    - "P" general (Box 9, Folder 238)
    - Park Department (Box 9, Folder 239)
    - Parking Authority (Box 9, Folder 240)
    - Public Works (Box 9, Folder 241)
    - Purchasing Agent (Box 9, Folder 242)
    - "R" general (Box 9, Folder 243)
    - Redevelopment (Box 9, Folder 244)
    - Rent control (Box 9, Folder 245)
    - "S" general (Box 9, Folder 246)
    - "T" general (Box 9, Folder 247)
    - Traffic (Box 9, Folder 248)
    - "U" general (Box 9, Folder 249)
    - Unions (Box 10, Folder 250)
    - United Illuminating Company (Box 10, Folder 251)
    - Veterans information (Box 10, Folder 252)
    - "W" general (Box 10, Folder 253)
    - Welfare, Department of (Box 10, Folder 254)
    - "Y" general (Box 10, Folder 255)
  - 1957
    - "A" general (Box 10, Folder 256)
    - Airport (Box 10, Folder 257-258)
    - Aldermen, Board of (Box 10, Folder 259)
    - Animal Shelter (Box 10, Folder 260)
    - Aquarium (proposed) (Box 10, Folder 261)
    - Assessors, Board of (Box 10, Folder 262)
    - Averill, Heman B. (Box 10, Folder 263)
    - "B" general (Box 10, Folder 264)
    - Band concerts and block dances (Box 10, Folder 265)
    - Budget (Box 10, Folder 266)
    - Building Department (Box 10, Folder 267)
    - "C" general (Box 10, Folder 268)
    - Cabinet (Box 10, Folder 269)
    - Capital Budget Program (Box 10, Folder 270)
    - Citizens Action Commission (Box 10, Folder 271)
    - City Court (Box 10, Folder 272)
    - Civil defense (Box 10, Folder 273)
    - Connecticut, State of: General Assembly (Box 10, Folder 274)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 10, Folder 275)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 10, Folder 276)
    - "D" general (Box 10, Folder 277)
    - Detzer, Karl (Box 10, Folder 278)
    - Dilieto, Biagio (Box 10, Folder 279)
    - "E" general (Box 10, Folder 280)
    - Education, Department of (Box 10, Folder 281-282)
    - Education, Department of: High Schools (Box 11, Folder 283)
    - Employees Retirement Fund (Box 11, Folder 284)
    - "F" general (Box 11, Folder 285)
    - Fair Rents, Commission on (Box 11, Folder 286)
    - Finance, Board of (Box 11, Folder 287)
    - "G" general (Box 11, Folder 288)
    - Golden, John M. (Box 11, Folder 289)
    - "H" general (Box 11, Folder 290)
    - Harbor (Box 11, Folder 291)
    - Harper's Magazine article (Box 11, Folder 292)
    - Health, Department of (Box 11, Folder 293)
    - Housing (Box 11, Folder 294)
    - Human Relations Advisor (Box 11, Folder 295)
    - Human Relations Council (Box 11, Folder 296)
    - Invitations (Box 11, Folder 297)
    - "K" general (Box 11, Folder 298)
    - "L" general (Box 11, Folder 299)
    - Light of Freedom (Box 11, Folder 300)
    - "M" general (Box 11, Folder 301)
    - N. A. A. C. P. (Box 11, Folder 302)
    - New Haven Clock & Watch Co. (Box 11, Folder 303)
    - New Haven Water Co. (Box 11, Folder 304)
    - News clippings (Box 11, Folder 305)
    - Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation (Box 11, Folder 306)
    - "P" general (Box 11, Folder 307)
    - P. T. A. (Box 11, Folder 308)
    - Park Department (Box 11, Folder 309)
    - Parking Authority (Box 11, Folder 310)
    - Public Works, Department of (Box 12, Folder 311)
    - Public Works, Department of: jobs (Box 12, Folder 312)
    - Purchasing Agent (Box 12, Folder 313)
    - "R" general (Box 12, Folder 314)
    - Redevelopment (Box 12, Folder 315)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street, general (Box 12, Folder 316)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street, Hill Junior High School (Box 12, Folder 317)
    - Redevelopment: congratulatory (Box 12, Folder 318-319)
    - Redevelopment: federal aid (Box 12, Folder 320)
    - Redevelopment: flea market (Box 12, Folder 321)
    - Redevelopment: Hotel Garde (Box 12, Folder 322)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 323)
    - Redevelopment: Oak Street (Box 12, Folder 324)
    - Redevelopment: other cities (Box 12, Folder 325)
    - Redevelopment: relocation (Box 12, Folder 326)
    - Redevelopment: Savitt case (Box 12, Folder 327)
    - Redevelopment: South Boulevard (Box 12, Folder 328)
    - Redevelopment: Wooster Square (Box 12, Folder 329)
    - "S" general (Box 12, Folder 330)
    - Scholarships (Yale) (Box 12, Folder 331)
    - Southern New England Telephone Company (Box 13, Folder 332)
    - State Teachers College (Box 13, Folder 333)
    - Tax Office (Box 13, Folder 334)
    - Time article (Box 13, Folder 335)
    - Traffic (Box 13, Folder 336)
    - "U" general (Box 13, Folder 337)
    - Unions (Box 13, Folder 338)
    - United Fund of Greater New Haven (Box 13, Folder 339)
    - U. S. Conference of Mayors (Box 13, Folder 340)
    - Unlicensed attendants (Box 13, Folder 341)
    - "V" general (Box 13, Folder 342)
    - Veterans information (Box 13, Folder 343)
    - Visiting Nurse Asscociation (Box 13, Folder 344)
    - "W" general (Box 13, Folder 345)
    - Welfare, Department of (Box 13, Folder 346)
    - "YZ" general (Box 13, Folder 347)
    - Yale University (Box 13, Folder 348)
    - Zoning appeals (Box 13, Folder 349)
  - 1958
    - "A" general (Box 13, Folder 350)
    - Airport (Box 13, Folder 351)
    - Aldermen, Board of (Box 13, Folder 352)
    - Aldermen, Board of "State of the City" message (Box 13, Folder 353)
    - Animal shelter (Box 13, Folder 354)
    - Anonymous (Box 13, Folder 355)
    - Architects (Box 13, Folder 356)
    - Arts festival (Box 13, Folder 357)
    - Assessors, Board of (Box 13, Folder 358)
    - Averill, Heman B. (Box 13, Folder 359)
    - Averill, Heman B. (Box 14, Folder 360)
    - "B" general (Box 14, Folder 361)
    - Budget (Box 14, Folder 362)
    - Building Department (Box 14, Folder 363)
    - "C" general (Box 14, Folder 364)
    - Capital Budget Program (Box 14, Folder 365)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 14, Folder 366)
    - Charter (Box 14, Folder 367)
    - Citizens Action Commission: general (Box 14, Folder 368)
    - Citizens Action Commission: Sweet, H. Gordon (Box 14, Folder 369)
    - City Engineer (Box 14, Folder 370)
    - City Plan: Andrews, Norris (Box 14, Folder 371)
    - City Plan: Fisher, Clyde (Box 14, Folder 372)
    - City Plan: zoning (Box 14, Folder 373)
    - Civil Defense (Box 14, Folder 374)
    - Clean-up campaign (Box 14, Folder 375)
    - Connecticut Company (Box 14, Folder 376)
    - Connecticut, State of: general (Box 14, Folder 377)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 14, Folder 378)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 14, Folder 379)
    - "D" general (Box 14, Folder 380)
    - Di Lieto, Biagio (Box 14, Folder 381)
    - Dixwell Community House (Box 14, Folder 382)
    - "E" general (Box 14, Folder 383)
    - Education, Department of (Box 14, Folder 384)
    - Education, Department of: high schools (Box 15, Folder 385)
    - Education, Department of: high school dedication (Box 15, Folder 386)
    - "F" general (Box 15, Folder 387-388)
    - Finance, Board of (Box 15, Folder 389)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 15, Folder 390)
    - "G" general (Box 15, Folder 391)
    - Golden, John M. (Box 15, Folder 392)
    - "H" general (Box 15, Folder 393)
    - Harbor (Box 15, Folder 394)
    - Health, Department of (Box 15, Folder 395)
    - Housing (Box 15, Folder 396)
    - Human Relations Advisor (Box 15, Folder 397)
    - "I" general (Box 15, Folder 398)
    - "J" general (Box 15, Folder 399)
    - "K" general (Box 15, Folder 400)
    - "L" general (Box 15, Folder 401-402)
    - "Mac" general (Box 16, Folder 403)
    - "M" general (Box 16, Folder 404-405)
    - Magazine articles: Life (Box 16, Folder 406)
    - Magazine articles: Life, response to (Box 16, Folder 407)
    - Magazine articles: Look (Box 16, Folder 408)
    - Magazine articles: Readers Digest (Box 16, Folder 409)
    - Magazine articles: Saturday Evening Post (Box 16, Folder 410)
    - Magazine articles: Saturday Evening Post, response to (Box 16, Folder 411)
    - Mayor's office (Box 16, Folder 412)
    - "N" general (Box 16, Folder 413)
    - N. A. A. C. P. (Box 16, Folder 414)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company (Box 16, Folder 415)
    - "O" general (Box 16, Folder 416)
    - O'Connell, William T. (Box 16, Folder 417)
    - Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation (Box 16, Folder 418)
    - "P" general (Box 16, Folder 419)
    - Park Department: general (Box 16, Folder 420-422)
    - Park Department; skating rinks (Box 16, Folder 423)
    - Public Works, Department of: Barbieri, Arthur T. (Box 17, Folder 424)
    - Public Works, Department of; general (Box 17, Folder 425-426)
    - Public Works, Department of: snow removal (Box 17, Folder 427)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 17, Folder 428)
    - "Q" general (Box 17, Folder 429)
    - "R" general (Box 17, Folder 430)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street (Box 17, Folder 431)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street hotel (Box 17, Folder 432)
    - Redevelopment: College Street extension (Box 17, Folder 433)
    - Redevelopment: Harbor Front area (Box 17, Folder 434)
    - Redevelopment: Logue, Edward J. (Box 17, Folder 435-437)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 438)
    - Redevelopment: Oak Street (Box 18, Folder 439)
    - Redevelopment: Oak Street Connector (Box 18, Folder 440)
    - Redevelopment: refinery (Box 18, Folder 441)
    - Redevelopment: relocation, business (Box 18, Folder 442)
    - Redevelopment: relocation, housing (Box 18, Folder 443)
    - Redevelopment: Route 5 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - Redevelopment: South Boulevard (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - Redevelopment: South Central (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - Redevelopment: Stevens-Lanigan (Box 18, Folder 447)
    - Redevelopment: Taylor, H. Ralph (Box 18, Folder 448)
    - Redevelopment: University Towers (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - Redevelopment: Wooster Square (Box 18, Folder 450)
    - Registrar of Voters (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham A. (Box 18, Folder 452)
    - Rock and roll (Box 18, Folder 453-454)
    - "S" general (Box 18, Folder 455-456)
    - Senate decision letters (Box 19, Folder 457)
    - "T" general (Box 19, Folder 458-459)
    - Town Clerk (Box 19, Folder 460)
    - Traffic (Box 19, Folder 461-465)
    - Travels (Box 19, Folder 466-468)
    - Travels (Box 20, Folder 469-473)
    - Travels: diary (Box 20, Folder 474)
    - Truman visit (Box 20, Folder 475)
    - "U" general (Box 20, Folder 476)
    - Unions (Box 20, Folder 477)
    - United Illuminating Company (Box 20, Folder 478)
    - "V" general (Box 20, Folder 479)
    - Villano, Peter F. (Box 20, Folder 480)
    - "W" general (Box 20, Folder 481-482)
    - Welfare, Department of (Box 20, Folder 483-484)
    - Welfare, Department of: Senior Citizens Day Center (Box 21, Folder 485)
    - Welfare, Department of: Springside Home (Box 21, Folder 486)
    - "XYZ" general (Box 21, Folder 487)
    - Yale University (Box 21, Folder 488)
    - Yale University: David S, Ingalls Hockey Rink (Box 21, Folder 489)
    - Zoning Board (Box 21, Folder 490)
  - 1959
    - "A" general (Box 21, Folder 491)
    - Airport (Box 21, Folder 492)
    - Airport (helioport) (Box 21, Folder 493)
    - Aldermen, Board of (Box 21, Folder 494)
    - Aldermen, Board of: Commission on Appropriations (Box 21, Folder 495)
    - Aldermen, Board of: Commission on Ordinances (Box 21, Folder 496)
    - All America City (Box 21, Folder 497)
      General note
      See also: oversize
    - Annex (Box 21, Folder 498-499)
    - Assessors, Board of (Box 21, Folder 500)
    - Averill, Heman B. (Box 22, Folder 501-503)
    - "B" general (Box 22, Folder 504-505)
    - Budget (Box 22, Folder 506)
    - Building Department (Box 22, Folder 507)
    - "C" general (Box 22, Folder 508-510)
    - Cabinet (Box 22, Folder 511)
    - Cabinet meetings (Box 22, Folder 512)
    - Citizens Action Commission: education (Box 22, Folder 513)
    - Citizens Action Commission: general (Box 23, Folder 514)
    - Citizens Action Commission: Heston, George (Box 23, Folder 515)
    - Citizens Action Commission: Quinnipiac Development Corporation (Box 23, Folder 516)
    - Citizens Action Commission: Sweet, H. Gordon (Box 23, Folder 517)
    - City Clerk (Box 23, Folder 518)
    - City Engineer (Box 23, Folder 519)
    - City Plan (Box 23, Folder 520)
    - City Plan; Andrews, Norris (Box 23, Folder 521)
    - City Plan: Andrews, Norris, zoning (Box 23, Folder 522)
    - City Plan: Fisher, Clyde (Box 23, Folder 523)
    - City Plan: zoning (Box 23, Folder 524)
    - Connecticut, State of: general (Box 23, Folder 525)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 23, Folder 526)
    - Connecticut, State of: Labor Department (Box 23, Folder 527)
    - Controller (Box 23, Folder 528)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 23, Folder 529-530)
    - "D" general (Box 24, Folder 531-532)
    - Democratic Advisory Council (Box 24, Folder 533-535)
    - Democratic Party (Box 24, Folder 536)
    - Democratic Town Committee (Box 24, Folder 537)
    - DiLieto, Biagio (Box 24, Folder 538)
    - Discrimination (Box 24, Folder 539)
    - "E" general (Box 24, Folder 540)
    - Education, Department of (Box 24, Folder 541-543)
    - Education, Department of: high schools (Box 25, Folder 544)
    - Education, Department of: high schools, Wilbur Cross dedication (Box 25, Folder 545)
    - Employees Retirement Fund (Box 25, Folder 546)
    - "F" general (Box 25, Folder 547)
    - Feriola, Peter (Box 25, Folder 548)
    - Finance, Board of (Box 25, Folder 549)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 25, Folder 550)
    - "G" general (Box 25, Folder 551)
    - Golden, John M. (Box 25, Folder 552)
    - "H" general (Box 25, Folder 553)
    - Harbor (Box 25, Folder 554)
    - Health, Department of (Box 25, Folder 555)
    - Health, Department of: Environmental Sanitation (Box 25, Folder 556)
    - Health, Department of: fluoridation (Box 25, Folder 557)
    - Housing (Box 25, Folder 558)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency (Box 25, Folder 559)
    - Human Relations Advisor (Box 25, Folder 560)
    - Human Relations Council (Box 25, Folder 561)
    - Humane Commission (Box 26, Folder 562)
    - "I" general (Box 26, Folder 563)
    - Israel (Box 26, Folder 564)
    - "J" general (Box 26, Folder 565)
    - "K" general (Box 26, Folder 566)
    - "L" general (Box 26, Folder 567-568)
    - La Guardia Award (Box 26, Folder 569)
    - Library (Box 26, Folder 570)
    - Lowe, Jeanne (Box 26, Folder 571)
    - "M" general (Box 26, Folder 572-577)
    - Mulvey, Harold (Box 26, Folder 578)
    - "N" general (Box 26, Folder 579-581)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company (Box 26, Folder 582)
    - "O" general (Box 26, Folder 583)
    - "P" general (Box 26, Folder 584)
    - Park Department (Box 27, Folder 585-588)
    - Park Department: Board of Commissioners (Box 27, Folder 589)
    - Park Department: ice skating rink (Box 27, Folder 590)
    - Park Department: zoo (Box 27, Folder 591)
    - Probate Court (Box 27, Folder 592)
    - Public Works, Department of (Box 27, Folder 593-600)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 27, Folder 601)
    - "R" general (Box 27, Folder 602)
    - Ramsey, William (Box 27, Folder 603)
    - Redevelopment: Appleby, L. Thomas (Box 27, Folder 604)
    - Redevelopment: bids for work (Box 27, Folder 605)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street (Box 27, Folder 606-607)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street, Stevens-Lanigan (Box 27, Folder 608)
    - Redevelopment: Harbor Front area (Box 27, Folder 609)
    - Redevelopment: Logue, Edward J. (Box 28, Folder 610-13)
    - Redevelopment: Long Wharf (Box 28, Folder 614)
    - Redevelopment: Medical Dental Center (Box 28, Folder 615)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 616-620)
    - Redevelopment: Mulligan, George (Box 28, Folder 621)
    - Redevelopment: Oak Street Connector (Box 28, Folder 622)
    - Redevelopment: relocation, business (Box 28, Folder 623)
    - Redevelopment: Route 5 (Box 28, Folder 624)
    - Redevelopment: South Boulevard (Box 28, Folder 625)
    - Redevelopment: Taylor, H. Ralph (Box 28, Folder 626)
    - Redevelopment: University Towers (Box 29, Folder 627)
    - Redevelopment: Wooster Square (Box 29, Folder 628-31)
    - Registrar of Voters (Box 29, Folder 632-633)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham A. (Box 29, Folder 634)
    - "S" general (Box 29, Folder 635)
    - "T" general (Box 29, Folder 636)
    - Traffic and Parking, Department of (Box 29, Folder 637-648)
    - Travels (Box 30, Folder 649)
    - "U" general (Box 30, Folder 650)
    - Unions (Box 30, Folder 651)
    - United Illuminating Company (Box 30, Folder 652)
    - "V" general (Box 30, Folder 653)
    - Villano, Peter F. (Box 30, Folder 654)
    - "W" general (Box 30, Folder 655)
    - Welfare (Box 30, Folder 656)
    - Welfare, Department of: Senior Citizens Day Center (Box 30, Folder 657)
    - Welfare, Department of: Springside Home (Box 30, Folder 658)
    - Welfare, Department of: Woodruff Center (Box 30, Folder 659)
    - "XYZ" general (Box 30, Folder 660)
    - Yale University (Box 30, Folder 661)
    - Zoning Board (Box 30, Folder 662)
  - 1960
    - "A" general (Box 30, Folder 663)
    - ACTION (Box 30, Folder 664)
    - ACTION: board meeting, Boston (Box 30, Folder 665)
    - ACTION: board meeting, New Haven (Box 30, Folder 666)
    - ACTION: board meeting, San Francisco (Box 30, Folder 667)
    - Administration (Box 30, Folder 668)
    - Administration (Box 31, Folder 669-671)
    - Administration: Circuit Court (Box 31, Folder 672)
    - Airport (helioport) (Box 31, Folder 673)
    - Annex (Box 31, Folder 674)
    - Arts, Festival of (Box 31, Folder 675)
    - Assessors, Board of (Box 31, Folder 676-677)
    - "B" general (Box 31, Folder 678-680)
    - Brewster estate (Box 31, Folder 681)
    - Building Department (Box 31, Folder 682)
    - "C" general (Box 32, Folder 683-684)
    - Cabinet meetings (Box 32, Folder 685)
    - "Cavaliere Ufficiale" Award (Box 32, Folder 686)
    - Christmas cards (Box 32, Folder 687)
    - Citizens Action Commission: Progress Pavilion (Box 32, Folder 688)
    - City Clerk (Box 32, Folder 689)
    - City Plan: Andrews, Norris (Box 32, Folder 690)
    - City Plan: Andrews, Norris, zoning (Box 32, Folder 691)
    - City Plan: zoning (Box 32, Folder 692)
    - Civil defense (Box 32, Folder 693-694)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 32, Folder 695-696)
    - Controller (Box 32, Folder 697-698)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 32, Folder 699-703)
    - Corporation Counsel: Mulvey, Harold (Box 33, Folder 704)
    - Cronin, William J. (Box 33, Folder 705)
    - "D" general (Box 33, Folder 706-710)
    - Democratic Party (Box 33, Folder 711-712)
    - "E" general (Box 33, Folder 713)
    - Education, Department of: elementary schools (Box 33, Folder 714-716)
    - Education, Department of: general (Box 33, Folder 717-723)
    - Education, Department of; high schools (Box 33, Folder 724-728)
    - Education, Department of: junior high schools (Box 33, Folder 729-730)
    - Education, Department of: 31st Ward (Box 33, Folder 731-733)
    - Engineering Department (Box 33, Folder 734)
    - "F" general (Box 33, Folder 735-736)
    - Feriola, Peter (Box 34, Folder 737)
    - Finance, Board of (Box 34, Folder 738)
    - "G" general (Box 34, Folder 739-742)
    - Golden, John M. (Box 34, Folder 743)
    - Grace-New Haven Hospital (Box 34, Folder 744)
    - "H" general (Box 34, Folder 745-749)
    - Health, Department of (Box 34, Folder 750)
    - Health, Department of: Environmental Sanitation (Box 34, Folder 751)
    - Health, Department of: fluoridation (Box 34, Folder 752)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency (Box 34, Folder 753)
    - Housing: Eastview Project (Box 34, Folder 754-757)
    - Human Relations Advisor (Box 34, Folder 758)
    - "I" general (Box 34, Folder 759)
    - "J" general (Box 34, Folder 760)
    - "K" general (Box 34, Folder 761)
    - Kennedy, John F. (Box 34, Folder 762)
    - "L" general (Box 35, Folder 763-764)
    - Legal Aid Bureau (Box 35, Folder 765)
    - Library (Box 35, Folder 766)
    - "Mac" general (Box 35, Folder 767)
    - "M" general (Box 35, Folder 768-769)
    - "N" general (Box 35, Folder 770)
    - N. A. A. C. P. (Box 35, Folder 771)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company (Box 35, Folder 772)
    - "O" general (Box 35, Folder 773)
    - "P" general (Box 35, Folder 774)
    - Park Department (Box 35, Folder 775-776)
    - Park Department (Box 36, Folder 777)
    - Park Department: commissioners (Box 36, Folder 778)
    - Personnel (Box 36, Folder 779)
    - Public Works, Department of (Box 36, Folder 780-782)
    - Public Works, Department of: incinerator program (Box 36, Folder 783)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 36, Folder 784)
    - "Q" general (Box 36, Folder 785)